AN EYE FOR IDEAS

CAITLIN IRONSIDE is a graphic designer based in Binghamton, New York. With a unique sensitivity to detail and a relentless curiosity that could kill a cat, she prides herself on noticing that which is often overlooked. Favoring a conceptual, research-led appraoch to design, Caitlin is passionate about both the analytical and the abstract. She strives to create outcomes which possess intelligence, beauty, relevance, and simplicity. Her favorite projects are those in which love of typograpohy and affinity for rich imagery can happily hold hands. To life's proverbial table she brings hard work, big dreaming, cheeky laughs, and a generous serving of sunshine.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Niskayuna High School '13

•Advanced Regents Diploma

Binghamton University '18

- •Bachelor of Fine Arts Graphic Design
- •Bachelor of Arts Psychology

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Freelance Design / May 2015 - Present

•Managed various branding, print, and web projects.

The Invisible Illnesses / July 2017-Present Creative Director

- •Designed social media content for multiple platforms.
- •Maintained organization's website.
- •Designed monthly newsletter.
- •Designed apparel.

Pipe Dream / August 2017-December 2017
Intern

- •Designed layouts for all sections and resolved layout issues.
- •Constructed advertisements and infographics.
- •Communicated with Photo Department.

SKILLS

- •Front-end Coding (HTML, CSS, JavaScript)
- •Layout & Typography
- Illustration & Animation
- Product Photography
- Photo Editing
- •Branding & Packaging
- •E-mail Marketing